PRAKHHAR MAKHIJA

☑ prakhharmakhija@gmail.com❖ 613-795-1884

in LinkedIn⊕ Portfolio Website

Skills

Programming

C++ C#

JavaScript HTML - CSS ReactJS - JSX React Three Fiber Framer Motion

Software

Unreal Engine
Unity
Visual Studio
3DSMax
Photoshop
Illustrator
Premiere
Blender

Services

GitHub GitHub Pages Netlify Assembla Trello

Personal

Punctual Responsible Honest Challenge-Accepting

Professional Summary

Game and Front-End Developer with 3 years of combined experience excelling in Al Programming and Gameplay Elements such as Al and Player Interfacing, Player Movement, Networking, Level Elements and more.

Shifting the same knowledge onto Front-End applications made with React, Framer Motion and a 3D Web NodeJS Package called React Three Fiber.

Rewarded by being listed in Dean's Honor List for 4 Consecutive Terms: 2020 and 2021 (Winter and Fall). Looking for an Entry Level position.

References available upon request.

Education

Algonquin College

Game Development (3 Years Advanced Diploma) Specializing in Programming Cumulative GPA: 3.85 September 2019 - April 2022

Udemv

Modern React with Redux (3 Months) Summer of 2021 - <u>Certificate</u>

3D Programming with JavaScript and the Three.js 3D Library (1 Month) Summer of 2021 - Certificate

Experience

Capstone Project

Al and Gameplay Programmer for Particle Interactive (8 Months) Implemented Al with Behaviour Trees C++, Grapple Hook, etc Working on Project Steelwalker over the course of a school year. September 2021 – Current

Dreamlight

Gameplay Programmer for Tapscone Studios (4 Months)
Implemented multiple gameplay features including AI, Event Triggers and
Gameplay Elements such as Kill Boxes, Moving Platforms, Checkpoints, etc.
All documented and available upon request.
January 2021 – April 2021

Particle Interactive Company Website - Link

Hosted on Netlify, made using ReactJS and maintained using GitHub. November 2021